affise.com 2017-02-18

# Affise - Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy (the “Policy”) describes how Aditec Solutions UAB (“Aditec Solutions”, “us”, or “we”) uses and discloses personally identifiable information that is collected by us or provided by you when you visit our website located at www.affise.com (the “Website”) or use our services (the "Services"). At Aditec Solutions, we are committed to respect the privacy choices of our clients and Website visitors. By accessing the Website or using our Services, you become subject to this Policy. Your acceptance of the terms of this Policy, in their entirety, shall be effective to your employees, if any. 

**1\. Definitions**

1.1. “Cookies” are small files that the Website or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the Website's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

1.2. “Personally Data” is information that directly, or when used in conjunction with other provided information, enables the identification of a specific individual.

**2\. Types of Information Collected**

2.1. Contact Information: When you use the Website or register / sign up for the Services, we may collect certain contact information from you, such as your first and last name, organization name, city, state and zip code, email address, and phone number or other contact details to help you with your experience (collectively, "Contact Information"). When purchasing Services, you will be required to provide additional information that may include a credit card number or other banking or payment information ("Billing Information"). This information is required by us to verify your identity, to establish your company’s account, and set up your Services. Generally, the Contact and Billing Information will be or will include Personal Data. 

2.2. Site Information and Cookies: We may use Cookies, web beacons and other technical means to collect and analyze certain information about how you and other visitors use the Website. This technical information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser information, and the preceding and succeeding websites you have visited, among other things. We may also keep a record of which pages of the Website you visit, and how long you spend on each page. Cookies can also be used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current Website activity, which enables us to provide you with improved Services. We also use Cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better Website experiences and tools in the future. 

We use Local Storage (HTML5), and our third party utility partner uses Local Shared Objects (Flash cookies) and Local Storage (HTML5) to store content information and preferences, and to display advertising based on your web browsing activity. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. You may set your browser to notify you or decline the receipt of Cookies; however, certain features of our Website or Services may not function properly or be available if your browser is configured to disable Cookies. 

2.3. Service Information: In order to provide Services to you and to improve our Services, we may collect information that is created or provided by you in connection with your use of the Services (collectively, “Service Information”), including order information, chat logs, email logs and information about your actions in various client areas on the Website. Service Information may include information that is Personal Data. We use Service Information to market our Services to you in a more personalized manner.

2.4. Third Party Information: We may obtain information about you from other sources and add it to your account Contact Information. This combined information may be used by us to enhance our ability to provide Services to you, to ensure that we are paid for Services, to advertise or market our business, and to tailor offers, promotions, etc. Thus, for instance, if you provide us with your email address, we may send you emails informing you about our services, products, offers, promotions and partnerships. The third party information may include information that is Personal Data. 

**3\. Use of Information Collected**

In addition to the uses described above, we may use information collected from you when you use Services, register or sign up for the Services, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or to our marketing communication, browse our Service, or use Website or its features in the following ways:   
3.1. We will use your Contact Information and Billing Information to provide Services and to provide you with access to the Services you have ordered, as well as support services, technical updates or updates on changes in our usage policies. We may also use your Contact Information to send you company updates and marketing offers when permitted by law and/or when you have agreed. You may refuse or revoke your consent to use Personal Data for the above purposes at any time by sending an email to us. If you are not a client of Aditec Solutions, we will use your Contact Information only for the purpose for which such information was provided. For example, if you have signed up to receive product information from us, we will use your Contact Information only to send you that information. 

3.2. We will store and use Service Information for the purpose of conducting business with you. Use of the Service Information is also governed by the agreements you enter into with us in connection with the Services (the “Services Terms”). Please refer to the Services Terms for specific provisions concerning confidentiality and data protection. In the event of any conflict between this Policy and the Services Terms, the Services Terms will prevail. 

3.3. We may use any information collected from you: (i) to personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested; (ii) to improve our Service in order to better serve you and/or to provide Services more effectively; (iii) to allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests, (iv) to ensure continuous improvement and development of the Services; (v) to administer the Website and to diagnose possible problems; (vi) to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other Website feature; (vii) to send periodic emails regarding your order or our other products and services. 

**4\. Disclosure of Information**

4.1. We may use third party suppliers/vendors to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include data storage services, database maintenance services and payment processing. When we employ such third party suppliers/vendors to perform services on our behalf, we will only provide them with access to Personal Data that they need to perform their specific function. We will put our reasonable efforts that each third party supplier/vendor will be required by contract to keep such Personal Data confidential and not to use it for any purpose other than providing services to us. 

4.2. We may share Personal Data with the owner of intellectual property rights to the Website and software used on it and to the extent needed to perform certain business-related functions (e.g. updates, maintenance, support, etc.) and for the purpose of providing Services to you. 

4.3. We may share Personal Data with entities that are controlled by or under common control with Aditec Solutions (each, an “Affiliate”) for the purpose of assisting Aditec Solutions in providing its Services to you. In that event, any such Affiliate will use Personal Data solely as permitted under this Policy. 

4.4. We may disclose Personal Data if required to do so by law or to comply with a legal obligation, or if we believe in good faith that such action is necessary to: (i) protect the rights or property of Aditec Solutions and its Affiliates or (ii) protect the property or safety of (xi) users of the Website or the Services; (xii) legal owners of the Website or the Services; or (xiii) any third party. If we will be required by law to disclose any of your Personal Data, we will use reasonable efforts to provide you with notice of that disclosure requirement, unless we are prohibited from doing so by statute, court or administrative order. 

4.5. We reserve the right to sell, assign or transfer our business or assets. In any such event or similar event, including but not limiting to corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, etc., Personal Data may be part of the transferred assets. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer or successor of Aditec Solutions may continue to use your Personal Data as set forth in this Policy. 

4.6. Please note that your non-personally identifiable information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, statistics or other uses. 

**5\. Security**

We will maintain industry-standard physical, electronic and procedural safeguards designed to protect data in our possession from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access. When we transmit highly confidential information (such as a credit card number) over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. However, no method of transmission or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. We regularly test and update our technology to help protect your data. However, such precautions do not guarantee that our Website or the data stored during your use of the Services is invulnerable to hacking and will not be subject to a security breach. We make no warranty, guarantee, or representation that the Website or the Services are or will be protected from all viruses, security threats or other vulnerabilities or that your information will always be secure. 

**6\. Links to Other Sites**

For the convenience of our visitors and clients, the Website may contain links to other sites, such as those of our partners or vendors, which are subject to different privacy policies. The Policy will not apply to your use of other websites. While we generally try to link only to sites that share similar high standards and respect for privacy, we have no responsibility or liability for the content, products or services offered, independent actions, or the privacy and security practices employed by these other independent sites. We encourage you to ask questions and review the applicable privacy policies found on such other websites, services and applications to understand how your information may be collected and used on these independent sites before disclosing information to third parties. 

**7\. Social Media & Widgets**

Our Website includes and/or may include social media features and widgets, such as the Facebook, Twitter or Linkedin button (the “Features”). These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our Website, and may set Cookies to enable the Feature to function properly. Features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Website. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

**8\. Minors**

We will never knowingly collect any Personal Data and personal information about individuals under eighteen (18) years of age. If Aditec Solutions obtains actual knowledge that it has collected personal information about an individual under eighteen (18) years of age, that information will be immediately deleted from our platform. 

**9\. Updates, Questions and Complaints**

9.1. You may update or delete Personal Data in our database (including Contact and Billing Information that you have provided to us) by contacting us at [support@affise.com](mailto:support@affise.com). If you delete information, we will only retain such copies of the information as are necessary for us to comply with governmental orders, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, or enforce any agreement you have entered into with us. 

9.2. In certain cases, you have the right to refuse / revoke consent to the processing of your Personal Data by contacting us at [support@affise.com](mailto:support@affise.com). Upon termination of processing of your Personal Data if can be difficult or impossible to provide Services to you. 

9.3. You can request information about all personal data we have stored about you by contacting us at [support@affise.com](mailto:support@affise.com). 

9.4. If you have any questions, concerns or complaints regarding the way we collect and handle your information, please contact us by email at [support@affise.com](mailto:support@affise.com) or Aditec Solutions UAB, Mokslininkų str. 2A, Vilnius, the Republic of Lithuania.
